Then.
那
Give me a glass of similar one.
来杯差不多的
Pour a glass to Mr. Yu.
给于总倒一杯
Give a try of my stock.
尝尝我的存酒
Okay.
好
Thanks.
谢谢啊
It smells good.
酒不错
If that's how you drink it.
你要是这么喝的话
Then give him something else.
那给他换点别的吧
Hit me another drink.
再给我来一杯
Okay.
好
Zhou Yao, I just want to ask you.
周耀 我就想问问你
Why?
为什么呀
Why does your Yaohui Co.
你的耀辉集团
not invest in
为什么不投我的
my Blue Ocean Media?
蓝海传媒
For a lot reasons.
有很多原因
But I'm not the only one
但也不是我一个人
who can call the shots.
能说了算
My Blue Ocean Media
我的蓝海传媒
is top-notch locally.
在本地那是天花板
My business is top 1 of the field.
我是第一 在本行业内
Isn't that right?
对不对
Why did you not invest?
为什么不投
We invest in the future,
我们投的是未来
the trend,
是趋势
but not present.
不是现在
Now your Blue Ocean Media is the top.
你蓝海传媒现在是第一
What about tomorrow?
那明天呢
Will it be No.1, too?
也会是第一吗
I give you my word.
我向你保证
My Blue Ocean Media
我蓝海传媒
was,
过去
is,
现在
and will be
未来
always the top 1.
永远都是第一
As long as your Yaohui Co.
只要你的耀辉
recognizes me,
对我有认可
my company can make transition.
我就能实现我的转型
In the future, I'll still be on top.
我未来我还是天花板
Mr. Yu.
于总
We don't talk about business after work.
下班了咱不谈工作
Only drink, okay?
只喝酒好吗
Fine.
好
You're not willing to invest in my company anyway.
反正你也不愿意投我
Isn't that right?
对吧
It's Okay. It's Okay.
没关系 没关系的
Thank you.
谢谢
Ms. Zhang.
张律师
How'd the talk go
你跟于海那边律师
with the lawyer of Yu Hai.
聊得怎么样了
Mr. Yu
于总呢
has no objection to division of property.
对财产分割没有异议
But he wants custody too.
但是他也想要抚养权
Yet you're the mother.
可是你是母亲
You will have advantages.
是有优势的
Besides, I'd like to try
而且我想尽量以
to have discussions
协商的形式
with him.
来跟他谈
Then should I go further
那我是不是要进一步
to prove my financial capacity?
证明我的经济能力啊
If Yu Hai
如果于海
are not willing to give up custody,
不肯放弃抚养权的话
I would argue
我就主张
that Yu Hai and you
你和于海
started the business together.
是共同创业的夫妻
Stock rights of the company should be equally divided.
应该平分公司股权
Then, we should prepare for
这样子 我们就要做好
the lawsuit.
打官司的准备了
Mom.
妈妈
I need to go to the bathroom.
我想上厕所
Okay.
好嘞
Ms. Zhang, please wait a minute.
张律师 麻烦稍等一下
Come, I'll take you there.
来 妈妈带你去
Mr. Yu.
于总
If drinking is not for
喝酒是为了
enjoyment and fun,
轻松愉快
but for dullness,
要喝闷酒那就算了
then we'd better go home and sleep.
还不如回家睡觉
Take a rest.
休息休息
You can't drown your sorrows in alcohol.
借酒消愁愁更愁啊
Yes, I should go home.
是 我是该回家了
With you, a bachelor,
跟你个光棍
what can I talk?
我能说什么呀
You're right.
没错
I'm single.
我是光棍
But there are two types of bachelors.
但是光棍有两种
There's one that
有一种光棍呢
has unrequited love.
是得不到另一半
The other type, however,
而还有一种光棍
just has so many admirers
追求他的人很多
that he wants none.
但他并不想得到另一半
We call him
这种光棍呢
eligible bachelor,
也叫做钻石王老五
or golden bachelor.
黄金单身汉
No, this...
不是这
What's the differences?
有什么区别吗
What eligible bachelor?
什么就钻石王老五啊
I think there are differences.
我觉得还是有区别的
You're a golden bachelor?
你是钻石王老五啊
Where's the gold?
钻石在哪儿呢
Where?
哪有钻石
Is your hair gold?
你头发是钻石
Or the ears?
耳朵是钻石
Or the nose?
还是这鼻子是钻石啊
To be honest,
说实在的
you don't have a wife
你不就是没媳妇
nor a child,
没孩子
and will go to the nursing home
将来就是进养老院
as a lonely old man.
就是一孤寡老人吗
Right?
对吧
In another twenty years,
再过二十年
if no one comes to the nursing home
养老院里边
to see you
要是没有人去看你
and visit you...
没有一探望的人
You're drunk.
你喝醉了
Am I right?
对不对
I'm leaving.
我先走了
Send Mr. Yu home.
送于总回去
Wait...
不是
Mr. Zhou.
周总
-Wait, -What are you doing?
不 你要干什么
Mr. Zhou, listen to me.
周总 你听我说
Listen.
你听我说
I talk too much today.
我今儿话多了
I'm begging you.
我求求你
Begging you to look
我求求你再看看
at our proposal
我们蓝海的方案
and my plan. Okay?
跟我的策划 好不好
You're drunk.
你今天喝醉了
No, my..
不是 我
Blue Ocean...ten years ago...
我蓝海我十年前
grew wildly
我十年前的蓝海
ten years ago.
那是野蛮生长
But if...
但是如果
I have your funding.
我有了你们的这笔投资
I promise...
我保证
No, no, trust me.
不 不 你相信我
Can you trust me?
你相信我好不好
I'm a
我是一个
decent media professional.
正经的传媒人
I have a media dream.
我有一个传媒梦
Alright?
好不好
For my business,
我为了我的蓝海
I've been working so hard for over ten years.
我艰辛创业这十多年
For it
我为了它
I've put everything I had.
我倾注了我的一切
But now I...
我现在
I lost
我连老婆孩子
my wife and kids.
我都没有了
You trust me.
你相信我
I absolutely
我绝对
would not fail your funding.
不辜负你们投的这些钱
Alright?
好不好
Some other day.
我们改天
No, no, no.
不不不
We must add WeChat.
咱俩一定得加个微信
Add a contact, okay?
加个微信 好不好
Add a contact.
加个微信
I send my proposal to you.
我把我的方案发给你
Okay? We add a WeChat.
好不好 我加个微信
Add a WeChat, alright?
加个微信 好不好
Wait.
你等等 等等
Let's add a contact.
我加个微信
Is this your wife?
这是你太太吗
Yes.
对
Now she is my wife.
现在是我太太
Not sure for the future.
以后就不一定了
Here, add a WeChat,
来 咱俩加个微信
okay?
加个微信 好吗
I send my proposal to you.
我把我的方案发给你
Fine, we add a WeChat.
好 加 加个微信
Okay.
好
Okay, scanned it.
好 扫上了
I'm sending to you now.
我这就给您发方案啊
I...
我
Look.
您看
How lovely my daughters are.
我这俩女儿多可爱呀
You can't be single.
不能当单身汉啊
Marry and have children.
娶妻生子
Have two daughters.
生俩女儿
So adorable.
太可爱了
I'm sending my proposal to you.
我给您发我的方案
Have a good rest.
好好休息
Are you okay?
你没事吧
I...
我
Mom.
妈妈
Will I see
我以后还会
daddy again?
再见到爸爸吗
Of course.
当然可以啊
Mom promises you.
妈妈跟你们保证
Every week in the future,
以后每一周啊
you can see daddy, alright?
都能见到爸爸 好不好
Be my girl. And go to sleep.
乖 快睡觉去吧
Cover yourself well.
盖好被子啊
Excuse me, Ms. Zhang.
张律师 不好意思啊
I was thinking
我刚在想啊
we'd better
咱们跟对方呢
negotiate a solution with them,
还是尽量协商解决
better not go to court.
最好不要打官司
I hope the kids can get
我希望孩子们得到
maximum protection.
最大的保护
Yes.
好的
Wanzhen, you really are
婉真 你真是我见过的
the most rational person
在离婚纠纷里
I've ever seen in a divorce dispute.
最理智的离婚当事人了
Am I?
是吗
Since I'm not for
毕竟我离婚
a fit of pique to divorce,
不是为了赌气
but for a better future,
而是为了有更好的未来
right?
不是吗
Wanzhen,
婉真
now that you've chosen this,
既然你选择了这条路
there must be much trouble
后面肯定还有很多
that follows.
不容易的事情
I will be on your side.
我一定会站在你这边
For anything you need,
你要有什么需要的
I will surely help you.
我一定帮助你
Thanks for the trouble, Ms. Zhang.
那拜托您了张律师
Thanks.
谢谢啊
Goodbye.
再见
Mr. Yu.
于总
The supplementary materials of Blue Ocean,
蓝海传媒的补充材料
please provide.
提供一下
Morning, Mr. Zhou.
周总 早
Mr. Yu.
于总
Here, the materials you asked.
那个 这 您要的资料
You're right last night.
你昨晚说得没错
No, I...last night,
不 我 我昨天晚上
talked too much.
话有点多
Don't take it seriously.
您别往心里去啊
Which one?
哪句话别往心里去
Investing in Blue Ocean,
投蓝海
or saying I'm a bachelor?
还是说我是个光棍
I...I meant investing in Blue Ocean
我 我是说投蓝海
is well worth it.
是非常值得投的
The other one, you forget about it.
后面那句您就当我没说
I was in a bad mood,
我心情不太好
so I was frivolous.
所以有点失态
You are too old to have love concerns.
多大年纪还为情所困
Let me see if you
我看你是不是
almost are a bachelor, too?
也快成光棍了
Let me do it.
我来 我来 我来
Keep in touch on the phone.
电话里常联系啊
Are you going to interview?
是要去面试吗
Mei Yiduo told me that
梅一朵跟我说啊
the senior,
我那师哥
dean Ma -
马院长
His college has a laboratory
他们学校有一个实验室
just needing a position
正好缺一个技术维修的
for technical maintenance.
负责人
So we have an appointment today
这不今天约了我
to talk.
去谈一谈
What's wrong?
干吗呀
I want to give you
想把我今天的好运气
all my good luck today.
都给你
Just today?
就只有今天吗
I haven't got the tomorrow's yet.
明天的我还没拿到呢
What are you doing?
干什么呢
I'm still here.
我还在呢
I just feel your dad
我就觉得你爸
pretty handsome today.
今天挺帅的
What's the matter of a hug?
抱一下怎么了
Yunjie...
云阶
What are you doing?
你干吗呀
What's going on?
你干吗呀 你这是
Let go.
你松开
Let him go.
松开
I also think my dad handsome.
我觉得我爸也挺帅的
What's wrong with my hug?
我也想抱一下 怎么了
He's my husband.
那是我老公
He's my dad.
这还我爸呢
Daddy.
爸爸
We are on the second in this bid.
这次投标 我们排第二
The first one
第一
is not a local company.
是一家外地公司
I don't know much about it,
我不是特别了解
and have asked people to find their information.
已经让他们去查资料了
It's okay.
没关系
It happens.
胜败乃兵家常事
We can win a bid,
咱能中一个标
which is already pretty good.
已经很不错了
Finish the job on hand.
把手头上的工作做好吧
The Yu Hai of Blue Ocean.
这个蓝海的于海
He should know this project.
他应该知道这个项目啊
Why didn't he come?
他怎么没来啊
I feel weird, too.
我也觉得挺奇怪的
Logically speaking,
按道理来说
Blue Ocean is kind of
蓝海也算本地的
a leading enterprise.
龙头企业了
They didn't attend...
他们没去
Do you think
你说会不会是
they have known better
他们知道
that they would not win the bid.
根本就不会中标
Therefore,
所以
they didn't attend.
就没参与啊
What's wrong?
干吗
Are you finding excuses for yourself?
你在给自己找借口啊
No, no, definitely not.
不不 那肯定不是啊
I am careful with
我哪个项目
each project.
都挺尽心尽力的
You should know it well.
这个您应该知道的呀
I know, I know.
我知道 我知道
I heard Yu Hai
我听说这个于海
and the director Huang
和他公司的
of his company
黄总监
have been discussed a lot
这闹得沸沸扬扬
in the city.
满城风雨的这
You were fellow students; did you know that?
你是他同学 你知道吗
I...
我
I've been busy
我最近不是一直在忙
with the biding lately,
投标吗
and I didn't know much about it.
没太关注
Haven't you said you want to take the annual vacation?
你是不是说要休年假
I was meant to say it.
本来还想跟您提这事呢
It's okay.
行
I've approved.
我批了
These days,
这段时间呢
the content department
这公司
in the company
这内容部
has a lot of things
这么一大摊子事
needing your management.
全你一个人管
You don't even have any help.
也没个帮手
It was exhausting.
确实是辛苦了
Just hang out
你啊 正好出去散散心
and relax yourself.
放松放松
I 'll arrange well the work
我会把手头工作
at hand.
都安排好的
Good.
好
There must be something wrong behind it.
事出反常必有妖啊
You know
你知道他为什么
why did he approve
那么痛快
the vacation so quickly?
把年假给你批了
There's something behind it?
这里头有事
He asked me to find headhunters
他让我找猎头
to look for a vice director.
物色副总监呢
And asked me to arrange
还让我安排
a new round of interview.
有一轮新的面试
How can't do these,
他不把你支开
if he doesn't send you away.
怎么干这事啊
Can't you promote
那你不能提拔一下
Mu?
阿木吗
He's been working with me for over 3 years.
他也跟了我三年多了
I'm sure
我觉得能力
his ability is fine.
肯定没问题的
You talk to him first then.
那你去跟阿木先谈一谈
I can put him in
我可以把他纳入
the list of personnel evaluation,
人事考核的名单里
but this thing
不过这个事吧
is still up to Mr. Zhang.
还是得看张总
What if the boss believes
万一人家老板觉得
people from the outside
外来的和尚
perform better?
念经更好听呢
You're right.
也是
Ms. Lan is the one
之前兰总
he found from outside
不就是他从外边
to balance me.
找来平衡我的吗
Right.
是
But those people
不过他们那些人啊
just know how to talk with Mr. Zhang.
就跟张总聊得热闹
They eventually left.
那不还来了又走了
The real core of the company
公司真正的核心
is you.
还得是你
That's what they call strength.
这就是实力
No, no, no. I mostly rely on you
不不不 主要是靠你
for offering news.
给我消息
No, no, no,
不不不
If the company does not
公司要没有
have the support of content department,
内容部门的支撑
no matter how great administrative department is,
行政部门再厉害
it would be useless.
也没有用
Without the effective management of administrative,
没有行政的有效管理
the content department can't grow either.
内容部门也是上不去的
This boasting talk
这商业互吹的感觉
is literally
真的是
pressure relieving.
太解压了
Then I go on.
那我继续
No need.
不用
Don't worry,
你放心吧
I'll help you for sure.
我肯定会帮你的
In case you want to have a baby again.
万一你又想生了呢
I've taken my leave.
我假都请了
I mean the next time.
我说的万一是下次
Think about it.
你想啊
Having a baby
这生个孩子吧
should take a year or so.
怎么也得个一年半载的
The vice director must come from inside.
副总监还是得找自己人
Have a baby as early as possible maybe.
要不你趁早吧
This time it is.
就这胎吧
Haven't you started menopause in advance?
你不都早更了吗
After this birth,
生完这胎
you still can recover,
还能缓缓
and make it to fifty years old.
怎么也能撑到个五十
Thanks a lot for your advice.
我谢谢你啊
You're welcome,
不用
I mean it.
真的
Delaying climacteric
延缓更年期这个事
is worth considering,
值得考虑
which has much to do
这跟生活质量
with the quality of life.
有很大关系
Get out.
滚
Okay.
好
My life quality is fine.
我生活质量没问题
Mu,
阿木
come over here.
来一下
Did you know
你们知不知道
why Haoze's mom
浩泽妈妈
was kicked out suddenly
为什么突然之间
by her husband?
被老公赶出去啊
Save a place
还不是给后面那女人
for the next woman.
留位置呀
No, no, no.
不不不
That's because
那是因为
the affair between her and that fitness coach
她和那个健身教练的事
was caught by her husband.
被她老公抓包了
Really?
真的
She even told us
她还跟我们说
that we should cultivate our spirit.
要修身养性呢
Turns out she is the one indiscreet.
原来自己这么不检点
Don't say that.
别这么说人家
Her husband is much so.
她老公也不好啊
He even had a child
跟别的女人
with the other woman.
连孩子都有了
Why don't you talk about her husband?
你们怎么不说她老公呢
Men and women are different.
这男人和女人能一样吗
That's right.
就是啊
What age is it now?
这都什么年代了
You are having double standards.
你们这叫双标
Here, have some snacks.
来来 吃零食
This one
这个
is good.
这个好吃
Take your time.
你们慢慢喝啊
I have to go.
我有点事先走
It has been 3 years since I was in the company.
来公司也三年了
How do you think of your performance?
觉得自己表现得怎么样
I've never been late or left early.
我没有迟到 没有早退
I'm willing to work overtime,
我心甘情愿地愿意加班
and enjoy working here.
我很享受在这里的工作
Then what?
然后呢
Then...
然后
Director Xu,
许总监
what do you want me to do?
你想让我干什么
What your plan
你对自己的职业
of your own occupation?
有什么规划吗
I have not.
没有
I...I just want to do my best
我 我只想努力干好的
to finish every job today.
今天每一件事情
Mu.
阿木啊
We can't just be like this.
咱不能这么木啊
We should have plan in workplace.
职场是要有规划的
You gotta know what kind of things to do
在什么时间做什么事情
at what time,
在什么时间
what kind of position to take,
做什么样的职位
at what time.
抓住什么样的机会
All these have to be planned.
这些都是要有计划的
Do you understand?
知道吗
I do.
知道
Want a promotion?
想升职吗
Want a pay raise?
想加薪吗
Of course.
想啊
Then you should mention it.
想你倒是提呀
Mention...
提
Our company just laid off some people.
公司刚刚结束了裁员
The content department has just been integrated,
内容部也刚刚整合
so the deputy director has been vacant.
副总监的位置一直空着
Why didn't you bring it up?
你为什么不提呢
You're now kind of
你在公司现在
a senior in the company.
也算是元老了
You can bring it up.
你可以提啊
How should I do?
我怎么提
Soldier's quality reflects
什么样的将军
the general's.
带什么样的兵
Listen to me.
听我说啊
First,
第一
write an application of promotion.
写一份升职申请
hand it over to HR.
交到人事部门
Put
要写上
your past work achievements,
你过往工作的成绩
and the outlook
以及对未来工作的
to your future.
展望
Second,
第二
you need to make efforts to show yourself lately,
最近你要努力表现一下
try not to make mistakes,
争取不犯错
and strive to do more,
努力做更多
alright?
好吗
Okay.
好
I'm bringing it up now.
我现在去提
Go head.
去吧
Thank you, director Xu.
谢谢许总监
Is this how promotion talk looks like?
这升职谈话是这样吗
Hi, Mengxin.
喂 心心
Sister,
姐
I've sent you a pin on your phone.
地址我发在你手机上了
Check it.
你看一眼
You...you...you...
你 你 你
you run to that place right now,
你现在赶紧往
hurry up.
往那个地方跑
I'm telling you...
我告诉你
Haowen...
老贾
Haowen has cheated on me!
老贾他出轨了
He has cheated on you?
老贾出轨了
Are you drunk?
你吃错药了吧
How's that impossible? I've shot it.
怎么不会 我拍到了
No..
不是
not me who shot it,
不是我拍的
but the paparazzi I asked shot it.
我找的狗仔
The paparazzi have caught it!
狗仔拍到了
What?
什么
Why am I here?
叫我来干吗呀
I was working, you know that?
我这上着班呢 知道吗
Haowen has cheated on me.
老贾他出轨了
I'm going to divorce.
我要跟他离婚
Then, go.
那走吧
What are you going?
你干吗去
Bust them.
捉奸啊
Wait.. you, you...
不是 你 你
you don't rush to stand up for me yet.
你先别着急替我出头
I'm not unreasonable.
我也不是无理取闹
Look, I have proof.
你看 我有证据的啊
See.
你看
He's having coffee with this woman.
他跟这女的在喝咖啡
You see, they're touching.
你看 勾肩搭背的
People make friends, right?
谁还不能交俩朋友吗
She's not a friend.
那不是朋友
She's an influencer.
那是女网红
So he can't make friend with an influencer?
网红不能交朋友
He can,
可以
but why
那为什么要在酒店
in the hotel?
交朋友呀
And going straight upstairs
而且喝完咖啡
after finishing coffee.
直接上楼了
What can it be?
说明什么
They must've booked a room in there.
说明他们房早就开好了
So what are you waiting for?
那你在这儿等什么呢
Hurry up,
赶快上去吧
more nagging,
再磨叽一会儿
they'd finish.
人家事都办完了
Then how could you bust them in bed?
你怎么捉奸在床啊
You don't say.
倒也不至于吧
In the room,
那在房间
maybe they're talking business.
没准是谈事呢
Then why did you call me here?
那你叫我来干吗
I'm scared.
我害怕呀
You see...
你 你说
He's hanging out with this woman,
他跟这女的在一块儿
and didn't even tell me.
他都没告诉我
What if I break in
那万一我进去一看
and saw something wrong?
真有点什么
What should I do then?
那我怎么办呀
Therefore,
所以你在意的点
what exactly is your problem?
到底是什么呀
Is he meeting a woman
是他跟一个女的见面
and did not tell you,
没有告诉你
right?
对吗
Let's not get angry
咱不生气啊
and afraid.
咱也不害怕
None of this is your problem,
这都不是你的问题
but the pregestational hormone.
是孕激素的问题
You're pregnant.
孕妇呢
You might be overthinking.
可能会多想一点
Sometimes you'd be a little suspicious,
有的时候会猜忌一点
but it's normal.
这都很正常
Now we figure it out,
那咱就把它弄清楚
okay?
好不好
Let's go check.
咱去看看吧
Could you be with me?
那你陪我一块儿去看看
Of course.
我来都来了 不陪你
You know why I'm here, don't you?
干吗呀
Come.
走吧
When will the pregestational hormone
孕激素什么时候
drop?
能降下来呀
I'm looking forward to our success.
期待着咱们能够成功
Me too.
期待
Good, good.
太好 太好
Can't wait to cooperate with you.
合作愉快 合作愉快
Mengxin.
心啊
Sister. Hi.
姐
what are you two doing here?
你俩怎么来这儿了
Let me introduce.
我给你介绍一下
This is a big influencer,
这是大网红
Ms. Lily.
莉莉姐
A super influence
超级网红
with millions of followers.
上千万粉丝呢
This is my wife Xu Mengxin,
这是我太太 许梦心
and my sister Xu Meng'an.
姐姐 许梦安
Mr. Jia, your wife is pretty.
贾总 你太太很漂亮
I don't look good,
我不好看
but I have a good taste.
但我审美好啊
All my family are beautiful,
那我们家人都漂亮是吧
so the foundation for our future cooperation
咱们以后合作基础
is very solid.
很强大了
I'm leaving.
我先走了
Okay, okay.
好好
Who is she?
谁啊
Are we going to do e-commerce.
咱不是要做电商吗
This is a super influencer
这可是超级网红
with millions of followers.
上千万粉丝的
I must be begging her
这以后我都得
to cooperate with me from now on.
求着跟她合作呢
I'm taking her to the factory
我先带她去工厂
to show her around.
参观一下啊
Eat whatever you want. It's all on me.
你们俩吃什么记我账上
-Okay.
好
-Sister,
姐
-Go, go, go.
快去吧 快去吧
-You stay with Mengxin.
你先陪着心啊
Not as pretty as I am indeed.
长得确实没有我漂亮
Mine is very good.
我这个真好喝
Try it.
你尝尝我的
No.
不喝
Take a sip.
你尝一口
How could you be like this?
你怎么这样啊
What?
怎么了
It's my first time to know
我第一次知道
someone who failed to bust cheating can react like this.
捉奸失败是长你这样的
My husband is not cheating on me.
那我老公没事
Shouldn't I be happy?
我可不高兴吗
Or maybe should I cry?
我不笑难道哭啊
This is our playfulness.
这是我们的夫妻情趣
You can't get it.
你不懂
The next time you two play,
你俩下次情趣的时候
don't get me involved, please.
能不能别叫上我
Mengxin,
心心
have you noticed
你有没有觉得
this pregnancy
你怀这一胎
feels different from the time
跟生熊熊的时候
you had Xiongxiong?
有点不太一样啊
I do think so.
我也觉得
I know, sometimes
我知道 我有时候
I do overreact.
确实做得有点过分
But I can't help it.
那我控制不住啊
How is that?
那为什么呢
Maybe
那可能是因为
I was thinking
生熊熊那会儿
Xiongxiong is the pledge of love
我觉得那是
between Haowen and me.
我和老贾爱情的结晶
But this time,
可是这个
I didn't want it at the beginning.
我一开始就不想要
You don't want it.
你不想要
You should have made a decision earlier.
你倒是早做决定啊
Look at this bump now.
现在挺着大肚子
Why are you still strolling around?
到处溜达什么呀
He wants this baby.
那老贾想要嘛
You're messing with him like this.
那你这么闹他
Didn't he react?
他都没啥反应吗
What reactions should he have?
他要有啥反应啊
He should be happy.
他应该高兴
That shows I love him.
那说明我爱他
I care about him.
我在乎他
Am I wrong?
我错了吗
Surely you're right to care about him,
你在乎他肯定是没有错
but the way you do it
但是你这么个在乎法
is wrong.
肯定是不对的
You asked someone to take picture of him.
你找人偷拍老贾的事
Does he know it?
老贾知道吗
Of course not.
当然不知道了
Are you idiot?
你是不是傻呀
If he knows,
他要知道了
it won't be candid photography.
那能叫偷拍吗
You must stop now.
你赶紧给我停了啊
Mengxin,
心心啊
you can make fun,
咱闹归闹啊
but the basic trust of a couple
但是夫妻间起码的信任
shall exist.
还是要有的
You can't tell him about it.
你别去跟老贾说啊
That depends on my mood.
那要看我心情了
Whom are you siding with?
哪头的你
Our family are all his side,
全家都是贾浩文那头的
obviously.
还用问吗
Did you know why Mom and Dad
你知道爸妈为什么
agreed you two got married?
同意你跟贾浩文结婚吗
At that time
虽然那个时候
he had nothing,
他一穷二白
and was nobody,
什么都不是
but
但是
he is really a good person,
他真的是个很好的人
not to mention he loves you so much
而且也真的爱你
and treats you well.
对你很好
If he...
那他
If he didn't love me,
那他要不是因为爱我
and treat me well,
对我很好
would I have the second child for him.
我能给他生二胎吗
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
不想跟你聊天了
Here, taste it.
给你尝尝这个
So sweet!
这么甜哪
Babies.
宝贝们
To our new home, here,
庆祝我们搬新家 来
cheers.
干杯
Thanks, mom.
谢谢妈妈
It would be great,
要是爸爸也能跟我们
if daddy was here with us.
一起吃就好了
Daddy is busy with work usually,
爸爸平时工作忙
but he will come on weekends
但是周末会回来
to have dinner
陪你们吃饭
and play with you.
带你们玩的
Oh, mom,
对了 妈妈
there's a classmate
我们班有一个
who is very close to me
跟我很要好的同学
is transferring to another school next week.
下周她要转学了
Why was that?
为什么呀
I heard her parents are divorced,
听说他爸爸妈妈离婚了
and cannot afford the tuition.
交不起学费
Nonsense.
别瞎说
Those are all guesses from classmates.
那些 都是同学瞎猜的
Can we
那 那我们不会
not afford the tuition either?
也交不起学费吧
I don't want to transfer to other schools.
我可不想转学
Don't worry.
放心吧
Mom has enough money.
妈妈有足够的钱
It definitely won't affect
绝对不会影响到
your lives and studies.
你们的生活和学习
But I heard daddy said
可是我听爸爸说
the money you earned every month
你每个月赚的钱
can't afford
都不够我们
our football class.
足球班的学费
Eat your food!
吃饭了
You talked too much.
就你话多
Though mom hasn't been
妈妈虽然很久
working for a long time,
没有工作了
mom can
但是妈妈可以
start from the beginning.
从头开始学啊
Just like you two,
那就像你们一样
we start from the first grade, right?
从一年级开始 对嘛
You won't
那你们不会
always be in the first grade,
一直上一年级
will you?
对不对
Then mom will study really hard,
那妈妈会努力地学习
and make more money
妈妈将来会
in the future.
赚更多更多的钱
Trust me.
要相信我啊
Mom, I believe in you.
妈妈 我相信你
You surely can do it.
你肯定行的
Thanks, my sweetheart.
谢谢宝贝
It's okay.
不客气
It's daddy!
是爸爸
Daddy.
爸爸
What are you doing? having dinner?
干吗呢 吃饭呢
Yes, I'm having dinner.
对 我吃饭呢
Here's a live stream for you.
来给你现场直播一下
See.
你看
Your favorite boiled shrimp,
有你爱吃的白灼大虾
Chunjiang fish,
还有春江鱼
bamboo shoots with pork,
还有笋丝烧肉
and braised pork.
还有红烧肉
That's great!
真棒
Where's your sister?
那个姐姐呢
Daddy.
爸爸
What are you eating?
吃什么呢
It looks so good.
这么香啊
Big shrimps.
吃大虾呢
Can you feed daddy one?
你喂爸爸一个啊
Sure.
可以啊
It tastes so good.
太香了
Having more for Daddy.
替爸爸多吃点啊
Daddy,
对了 爸爸
what are you eating for dinner?
你晚饭吃的是什么呀
Show us.
给我们也看看
Yes.
对啊
Me...?
我呀 这这这
Daddy is too busy with work
爸爸还工作呢
to have dinner yet.
还没顾得上吃饭呢
You have so much delicious food.
你们这吃这么多好吃的
It really makes me drool over.
馋死爸爸了
Feed daddy one more.
再给爸爸喂一个
Okay.
好
Daddy is able to reach it
爸爸也吃不到啊
but to eat the air, right?
吃空气了 是不是
What should I do?
你说爸爸又想你们了
Daddy is missing you.
怎么办呢
I can only make a video call.
打个视频呢 只能
Where's mom?
妈妈呢
Here.
这儿呢
Daddy.
对了 爸爸
Let me show you around
我带你参观一下
our new house.
我们的新家
Mom, you have it as well.
妈妈 你也吃吧
Thanks, sweetheart.
谢谢宝贝
You eat it, here.
你吃 来
Come.
进
Mr. Yu.
于总
The instant noodles you asked.
您要的泡面
Have you added what I want?
加的东西加了吗
Yes.
加了
Two spiced eggs,
给您加了两个卤蛋
ham sausage and luncheon meat for you.
还有火腿肠跟午餐肉
Good, thanks.
好嘞 谢谢
Let me show you daddy's dinner.
给你们看看爸爸的晚饭
A little bit of sadfishing.
有点卖惨啊
Come in.
进
Mr. Yu.
于总
Mr. Zhou, what brings you here?
周总 您怎么来了
Passing by.
路过
What are you eating? Instant noodles.
吃什么呢 泡面啊
Looks sad.
这么惨
No,
没有
some time in a while
这隔一段时间吧
I'd miss it.
就想方便面这味儿
I usually eat in the dining room,
平常老在餐厅吃饭
but I often think about
老想回想一下这个
this taste in college dorms.
上大学宿舍的味道
How nice!
这么豪华啊
Alright, then.
行 挺好的
I'm leaving.
那我走了啊
I came to Blue Ocean
我刚才到蓝海
and looked around.
转了一圈啊
Now Blue Ocean is on the
这个蓝海现在
inspection period.
不正考察期吗
I just take a look and leave now.
我看一眼就走
You're making a surprise check.
您这是搞突然检查啊
I'm not.
没有
Rest assured, Mr. Zhou.
周总 您放心
Blue Ocean has been the same
我们蓝海呢
as time went by.
十年如一日
We're absolutely transparent.
绝对公开 透明
Welcome investors to check at any time.
欢迎投资人随时来检查
Or I'll show you more specifically.
要不我再陪您详细看看
It's okay, It's okay.
不用了 不用了
I've seen it.
我看过了 差不多了
The future work would be taken over
后面的工作由两位那个
by these two investment managers.
投资经理接手
I have a business dinner
我附近啊
nearby,
有个商务饭局
and I passed by here.
我路过你这儿
That reminds me of you.
想起你这茬儿来了
If it's convenient,
要是方便的话
I can go with you.
我跟您一起
The bill is one me.
晚上我来买单
It's okay.
那不用了
Inconvenient.
不方便
You can't waste your
你别浪费了你的
nice instant noodles.
豪华的泡面
Alright, I'm leaving.
行了 走了
Eat it now,
你赶紧吃吧
or the noodles are getting dry.
面一会儿坨了
Take your time.
您慢走啊
The noodles...
我这面
Am I eating this at a good time?
吃得对还是不对啊
I sleep on the upper.
我要睡上铺
No.
不行
I've won so many times.
我都赢了那么多回
You are...you are cheating.
你叫 你这叫耍赖
You know that?
知道吗
I was not ready.
刚才没准备好
One more time.
再来一次嘛
-Rock, scissors, paper. -Rock, scissors, paper.
石头 剪刀 布
I won!
我赢了
No, I want the top bunk.
不行 我要上铺
Just let me.
你让着点我嘛
No.
不行
If you don't let me...
你要不给我的话
What are you fighting about?
你俩吵什么呢
Come down.
快下来
You can't get up tomorrow if you don't sleep.
再不睡觉明天起不来了
Mom,
妈妈
you say something to sister.
你管管姐姐
She doesn't let me sleep on the upper.
她非不让着我
She's the one who lost and cheated.
是她自己输了还想耍赖
Mom, you decide who is right.
妈妈 你评评理
You all want to sleep the top bunk, right?
都想睡上铺 对不对
What if one of you
那要不这样 我们
sleep for a week in turns?
一人睡一周 轮着睡
Then the first week is mine.
那第一周得是我的
No!
不行
Weren't you just talking to daddy,
你刚刚不是还跟爸爸说
saying big house is good?
大房子好吗
And now you're fighting me for the upper.
现在又跟我抢上铺
I've changed my mind.
我现在改变主意了
Now I think this is the best place.
我现在觉得这儿最好
The best place
全地球 全宇宙
in the world, in the universe
最好的地方
is this top bunk.
就是这个上铺
Alright, alright, enough of this.
行了行了 不吵了
How about tonight
要不今天晚上
you share the top bunk.
你们一起挤一挤上铺
Never mind, let her have it.
算了算了 让给她了
But we have to exchange next time,
下周这个时候交换地盘
or I won't talk to you if you cheat again.
再耍赖不理你了
Sister is the best, I love you.
姐姐最好了 我爱你
Hurry,
快
go to the bed,
上去睡觉去
otherwise, you can't get up tomorrow.
要不然明天起不来了
Cover yourself well.
被子盖好
Zhenzhen, cover yourself well.
真真把被子盖好了
Okay.
好
Turn off the little light.
把小台灯关掉
Goodnight, babies.
晚安 宝贝们
-Mom, goodnight. -Mom, goodnight.
妈妈晚安
-Goodnight.
晚安
Sister, the top bunk is really good,
姐姐 这个上铺真的好棒啊
better than the camping tent.
比露营的帐篷还棒
We made it a deal
说好了下周这个时间
to exchange this time next week.
交换地盘
I know, sister.
知道了 姐姐
Sister,
姐姐
you love this house,
你喜欢这个家
or the old one?
还是喜欢以前的家呀
I like both,
都喜欢
but mom lives in this house,
不过这个家有妈妈
so I like this better.
就更喜欢这个家
If
要是
there's one more bathroom,
这儿能再多一个洗手间
that would be great,
那就好了
or I have to fight with you
要不然每次上厕所
when I need to go to the bathroom.
都要跟你抢
If
要是
it can be closer to the school,
能再离学校更近一点
that's even better,
那就更好了
or,
要不然的话
we have to get up
每天都要早起
half an hour earlier.
半个多小时
You live in the school playground then.
那你住学校操场
That's the closest.
那儿离得最近
I can bring my bed
那能把这张床
there?
也搬过去吗
The top bunk is still mine.
我还要睡上铺的
Hurry to sleep.
快点睡吧
Whoever gets up early tomorrow
明天谁起来得早
can use the bathroom first.
谁就先用洗手间
Fine.
好
It's deal.
一言为定
No cheating.
不许耍赖
Zhenzhen, goodnight.
真真晚安
Goodnight, sister.
姐姐晚安
How's the talk with
今天跟马院长
Mr. Ma today?
聊得怎么样啊
Pretty nice.
聊得挺好
He told me
老马跟我说
to start work as soon as possible,
让我尽快入职
and check in next Monday.
下周一 就到单位报到
Next Monday?
下周一吗
Working at lab
虽然说实验室工作
can't make as much money as in enterprise,
赚的没有企业多
but once I'm on duty,
但是一旦我上了班了
our family
那咱们家的情况
would get better.
就能好起来啊
I was thinking
我本来还想下周
next week I'd take the annual vacation,
请个年假
and get the surgery,
把手术做了呢
but your job is a big deal,
但你这是大事
you check in first.
你先办入职
Meng'an.
梦安
Have you really
这个事
decided to do the surgery?
你真的想好了吗
To be honest?
说实话吗
No.
没有
But I don't think this is a good time to have a baby.
但我觉得我现在不能生
Zhang has been looking for someone else.
老张已经开始找人了
If I had a baby,
我要是真敢生
he'd lay me off.
他真敢让我下岗
If I lost my job,
如果我工作没了
our family would depend on you
那咱家不就又靠你
alone?
一个人了吗
It'd the same story as now.
那不跟现在一样了吗
No,
不对
it'd get worse.
还不如现在呢吧
What about you?
你呢
What do you think?
你什么想法啊
To be honest?
说实话吗
I want this baby.
我想要
You are so early.
这么早啊
I dropped my kids to school,
我送完孩子上学
then came over.
就过来了
The ones having children
这有孩子的人哪
get up early.
就是起得早啊
Here, Mr. Sun.
来 孙主任
Thanks.
谢谢
Mr. Sun,
孙主任
I want to discuss something with you.
我想跟您商量件事
Have a seat.
来 请坐
First, I'd like to thank you specially
首先我特别感谢您
for offering me this job,
给了我这份工作
however, I'd like to transfer to sales position,
但是我想转岗做销售
could you help me?
您能帮我想想办法吗
You want to do sales?
你要做销售
I want to make more money.
我想多赚钱
As far as I know,
据我所知啊
your home conditions are good.
你们家条件不错呀
Like the car,
咱就说这车吧
every day you come to work,
你每天上班的时候
you park it far away,
把车停得蛮远的
but actually, your car
其实你的车要比我的车
is better than mine.
好多了啊
You know,
你也知道
I used to
我
be a full-time wife.
以前在家是全职太太
The wealth is
那家里的钱
not earned by me.
也不是我赚的
You've seen the situation
我的家庭情况
of my family that day.
你那天也看见了
I'm going to divorce.
我现在打算离婚
I'm sorry about that.
对不起啊
I don't know much about that.
这种情况我不太了解
Are you seriously going to do this?
那真要离啊
We've already separated.
已经分居了
I'm working on the proceedings now.
正在走离婚手续
I'm fighting for
我在争取两个孩子的
the custody of two kids,
抚养权
therefore, I need higher
需要更高的
payroll statement
工资流水
to prove my financial capacity.
来证明我的经济能力
Besides, the kids have
而且孩子跟我
psychological gap
搬出来以后吧
after moving out,
心里有落差
I also want them to have confidence
我也想让孩子有信心
that there's no need to live a hard life
不至于跟着妈妈
with her mom.
过苦日子
Wanzhen.
婉真啊
Let me
我呀
be honest.
说句掏心窝子的话
Being a salesman
这个做销售啊
is not for everyone.
不是谁都能做的
I have also seen your resume.
我也看了你的履历
Your previous job
你以前的工作
is very decent.
非常的光鲜
Now you have two kids
而且你现在带着孩子
while doing sales
做这个销售啊
day and night.
没白没黑的
Sometimes you need to drink.
有时候还应付喝酒呢
Can you handle it?
你能行吗
If you did transfer
而且你真转了
to do sales,
这个销售啊
have you considered the minimum salary?
底薪想过没有
Almost zero.
那几乎就是个零
The worse situation is
弄不好连现在工作
you will lose your current position.
就丢了
So,
所以啊
think about it seriously,
你再好好想一想
then make a decision.
再做决定
Do it.
转啊
You have to.
必须得转啊
I do think so.
我也觉得应该转
And I just mentioned it to Mr. Sun.
才跟孙主任提的
But I think
但是我觉得
he got the point, too.
孙主任说得也有道理
If you don't do well in sales,
如果销售做不好
you might even lose the clerk position.
可能连文员都要丢了
Then what?
丢就丢呗
Find another one.
丢了再找啊
Let's not talk about how much money you can make.
咱先不说挣多少钱啊
In the case of a property enterprise,
就一家地产公司而言
the most important core department
最主要的核心部门
is sales.
就是销售
In a long-term plan,
长远打算
you should enter the core field of
你也要进入这家公司的
the company.
核心领域才行的
You're right.
没错
Hearing your view,
你这么一说
I feel peaceful now.
我心里就踏实了
But I still worry,
但是我还是担心
although I know a few women
我虽然认识几个
who can afford a house,
能买得起房的太太
how long can it be?
但是我能撑多久啊
Who cares?
管他呢
One day at a time.
能撑一天是一天呀
Distribute your sales to them properly.
合理分配了她们
Sell one house in a month.
一个月卖一套
At least for these months,
至少在这几个月里面
your performance and payroll statement
你的业绩和流水
are good.
都是漂亮的吧
It's enough for you to file a lawsuit,
足够支撑你打官司的
am I right?
对不对
If you really
你要实在心里头
don't believe in yourself,
没底的话
then improve yourself
那就边卖房
while selling houses.
边提升自己
When the day when
实在有一天
sales can't go on,
销售干不下去了
do something else.
咱就改行干别的
Maybe
没准还能
you can go up to a higher level,
更上一个台阶呢
right?
对吧
Right.
对
I know what to do now.
我知道该怎么做了
Come on!
加油啊
How do you do?
你怎么样啊
Have you talked about
孩子的事情
the baby thing with Li Lin?
跟李临说了吗
I have.
说了
What're you going to do?
你们怎么打算
No plans.
没打算
This is the first time
我跟李临这么多年
we've met something so tricky
好像还是第一次遇到
since we were together.
这么纠结的事
Thinking back,
现在想想啊
he was so happy
怀头胎那会儿
about the first birth
高兴
that he can't wait for
他恨不得让全世界人
everyone to know I was pregnant.
都知道我怀孕了
Now,
现在
all that he has is fear,
就剩下害怕
fearing one more person will know
生怕多一个人知道
I am pregnant.
我怀孕
I think the two of us
我觉得我们俩
are both afraid to
都不太敢
talk much about this subject.
就这个问题深聊
Like no one dares
好像谁都不敢
to make the decision.
做这个决定似的
You two...
你们俩
Don't get too anxious.
也别太焦虑了
Give yourselves more time.
给自己多一些时间
Don't make decisions lightly
不到最后一刻
till the final moment.
不要轻易做决定
After all,
毕竟
we're not young.
我们不年轻了
You're transferring to sales?
你要转销售
What about
那你现在的工作
your current job?
怎么办啊
I can balance
日常的行政工作
the daily administrative work.
我可以兼顾
Didn't you say
您不是说过吗
selling houses
在地产公司
in a property company is all that matters.
卖出房子就是王道
Recently.
最近呢
I've looked at
我也把房屋销售的
some information
这个资料
of house sales.
我都看了
I can do it.
我可以胜任
Wanzhen.
婉真
In fact, you can introduce customers
其实要有客源
to the sales department.
可以介绍给销售部
You don't have to
你不一定要自己去
do it by yourself.
当销售啊
And the sales department
而且我们销售部
is not under-staffed.
现在也不缺人
But I need this occupation.
可是我需要这份工作
Mr. Qian,
钱总
you don't have to answer me right now.
你不用马上回答我
I can start from now,
我可以先做起来
I've counted.
我算了一下
With the interpersonal network I have,
我手头的人脉资源
I guarantee
我保底
I can sell six houses.
能卖出六套房
Six?
六套
All we have this time is advanced houses.
我们这次可都是高等盘
They are all large ones.
全都是大户型的
Understand.
是啊
That's why
就是因为大户型
you need salesperson like me.
才需要我这样的销售
Look,
您看呀
who else in our company
我们公司
is better than me
有谁比我更合适
to sell this kind of high-end property?
卖这种高档楼盘
Sales is not one-shot deals.
销售可不是一锤子买卖
Whatever it is or not,
不管是不是一锤子买卖
but this shot
但是这一锤子下去
will bring you at least six houses.
至少是六套房啊
Would I
那这样我不会
offend Mr. Yu if so?
得罪你们家于总吧
That depends on what you want.
那要看您想要什么了
Compared to offend Mr. Yu,
和得罪于总相比呢
what you get
您得到的
is solid  performance.
可是实打实的业绩啊
Please consider it.
您考虑一下
Wanzhen.
婉真
If you can't bring results,
那你要带不来业绩
I may let you quit.
我可让你辞职走人了啊
No problem.
没问题
Chen Wanzhen,
陈婉真
are you going to transfer to sales?
你这是要转销售啊
Yes.
是啊
This way, Mengxin.
这边 老婆
It's okay.
没事
Your turn.
到你们了
Come.
走
Mengxin?
心
High progesterone values.
孕酮值偏高
But you don't need to worry.
不过你们也不要担心啊
Relax and adjust your mindset.
放轻松 把心态调整好
pay attention to sleep.
注意睡眠
It would be fine
把这个孕酮呢
after bringing down the progesterone.
降下来 就好了
It's okay, Mengxin.
没事 老婆
You should care more about
你要多关心一下
your wife's psychological state.
你老婆的心理状态
This is her report of
这是她的心理健康
mental health.
评估报告
Disqualified.
不合格
What should I do?
那怎么办呀
Take it easy.
你别着急
Here is the thing.
是这样的
The pregnant women's hormones
这孕妇呢 在怀孕期间
will be higher during pregnancy,
她的激素呢 都会偏高
which will lead to
也会导致她的
her emotional instability.
情绪不稳定
However,
孕妇呢
they can't take medicine
又在怀孕期间呢
during pregnancy.
她又不能吃药
Therefore,
所以说呀
family members should
你们家属呀
be more attentive to her.
就要多关心关心她
It's okay, Mengxin.
没事 老婆